

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER · IT SPECIALIST

■ (+01) 843-557-3014 | **■** Z5483Y@gmail.com | **☆** khuei.github.io | **©** khuei | **m** khuen

Summary_

Freshman undergraduate computer science student at Clemson University. 8+ years experience specializing in software development, infrastructure autonomation, and general information technology. Passionate about creating and improving softwares. Interested in improving problem-solving skills and gaining more experience.

Experience

Warp Drive Robotics Charleston, SC, US

LEAD SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

August 2018 - June 2021

- Developed softwares in C/C++ for VEX hardwares.
- Implemented control/motion/tracking algorithm.
- Designed easy-to-use user interface.
- Built an engineering journal recording framework.
- Automated trusted timestamping for git repositories.

BCUZ Robotics Clemson, SC, US

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

August 2021 - Present

• Developing efficient softwares for robots.

Projects.

- base16-fork An improved structured and regenerative base16 theme environment
- cbase16 A blazing fast base16 colorscheme builder
- tdr Text-based user interface utility to manage todo list
- timestamp trusted timestamp management for git

Education

West Ashley High Shool Charleston, SC, US

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

August 2017 - June 2021

- · Graduted 6th in the class of 2021
- Weighted GPA of 4.86

Clemson University Clemson, SC, US

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

August 2021 - Present

Honors & Awards

HIGH SCHOOL VEX ROBOTICS COMPETITIONS

2018	Design Award , The Cougar Challenge	Charleston, SC, US
2019	Sportsmanship, 2019 South Carolina VRC HS State Championship	Charleston, SC, US
2020	Excellence Award, Warrior Challence	Charleston, SC, US
2020	Think Award, Palmetto Scholars Academy Phoenix Rising Qualifier	Charleston, US
2020	Think Award, 2020 South Carolina VRC HS State Championship	Charleston, SC, US
2021	Think Award, 2021 South Carolina VRC HS State Championship	Greenville, SC, US

NOVEMBER 29, 2021 KHUE NGUYEN · RÉSUMÉ 1